http://www.basschamonix.com/privacy-policy

Ski Lessons in the Alps
"Making your Skiing our Passion"
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.basschamonix.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.   It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
“BASS Chamonix Limited”
BASS Chamonix operates the following brands and delivers these services through this website:
BASS Chamonix/Megeve/St Gervais (delivering ski lessons in these areas of France) as part of the British Alpine Ski School network (www.britishskischool.com)
Parallel Dreams (ski performance courses in UK & Europe, www.paralleldreams.co.uk)
"BASS Chamonix Limited." is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy notice.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name and contact information including email address and contact phone numbers
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests, other information relevant to customer booking, surveys and/or offers.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Allocating ski lessons & associated services.
Security
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send a promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail.
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
We partner with other third parties to provide specific services (self-employed instructors & mountain guides). When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us or emailing us at bookings@basschamonix.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the current Data Protection Act.  If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the Data Protection Officer (Mr D Tate), BASS Chamonix Limited, 90 Argyll Road, Kinross, Perth & Kinross-shire, KY13 8BL, Scotland. Email: derek@basschamonix.com
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
BASS Chamonix Limited
Company reg number SC267904, registered in Scotland
Enquire/Book Now
Get Social with us
Email:  bookings@basschamonix.com
© BASS Chamonix Limited  Terms of Use / Privacy policy.   Booking Conditions
